allaboardtoys.com 2009-12-31

# All Aboard Toys Privacy Policy

##  **Secure Shopping**

**All Aboard Toys Online Ordering Security**  
At All Aboard Toys, we use state-of-the-art proven computer technology to protect your personal information provided to us through our online ordering system. In addition, we will reimburse you as noted below in "Our Commitment to Your Credit Safety", if your credit card information is used fraudulently as a result of it being obtained illegally from our site or while in transmission to our site. Please see below for more information regarding our technology, and our commitment to your credit card and personal information safety. 

**Our Commitment to Your Credit Card Safety**  
The best testament to our commitment is the fact that no customer of All Aboard Toys has ever reported illegal use of a credit card in association with that card's use on AllAboardToys.com. While we are confident that our perfect record will stand, we will reimburse you if you do have a legitimate complaint of unauthorized use, according to the guidelines below. 

In adherence to the Fair Credit Billing Act, your credit card provider can only hold you liable for up to $50.00 of fraudulent charges. If your credit card provider holds you liable for an amount up to $50.00, AllAboardToys.com will reimburse you that amount. AllAboardToys.com will cover this liability only if the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own from purchases made at AllAboardToys.com. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures. 

Please address all communications to [Customer Care](http://demo.tystoybox.com/pages/Customer_Service), or by mail to: 

> AllAboardToys.com Customer Care  
>  7115 Industrial Road  
>  Florence, KY 41042

**What personal information does All Aboard Toys gather and what do you do with it?**  
**Order Information:** While you may browse our web site completely anonymously, in order for you to order and for us to ship an order to you, we must collect the following items which we consider personal information: 

\- The shipping destination name & address so we know where to ship your order.  
\- The billing name & address for payment verification purposes.  
\- Your e-mail address for notification purposes and optionally for newsletters (opt-in).  
\- Your phone number, in case we need to follow-up.  
\- A password to create an account for you (optional step) so you can track your orders.  
\- Credit card details if selected as method of payment. This information is deleted later.  
\- Customers who wish to pay with BillMeLater must provide the last 4 digits of your Social Security Number and your date of birth. This information is collected and used only for BillMeLater and is deleted later.  
\- Customers who wish to pay with electronic checks through Telecheck must provide a routing number, checking account number, driver's license number, and a driver's license state. This information is used only for processing electronic checks and is deleted later.  

**The All AboardToys Newsletter:** If you want to receive e-mail newsletters from All Aboard Toys with updates on sales, promotions and new arrivals, you must subscribe. You can subscribe to the All Aboard Toys newsletter using a link on the home page or by creating an account. 

We offer specialty newsletters created for customers with interests in specific age groups, brands, categories and promotions. When we launch a new specialty newsletter, we may e-mail it to you if you already subscribe to the All Aboard Toys newsletter and if your buying patterns indicate that the information might interest you. 

Each newsletter prominently displays a link you can use to unsubscribe at any time. We also include the e-mail address you used when you signed up for the newsletter, so you know which address to enter when you unsubscribe. 

**Contests:** From time to time All Aboard Toys features contests or special promotions. To participate, you must enter your name and e-mail address. We use your e-mail address to contact you only if you win the contest or special promotion. We add your e-mail address to our customer newsletter mailing list when you sign up for a contest. 

**Creating a WishList:** You may use our WishList to create a list of favorite products and to send e-mails to your friends. You must be a registered shopper with a valid password to modify or delete products from a WishList or to modify or delete the e-mail recipient list. Children under 13 may not create a WishList or Account unless they have direct supervision by a parent or guardian. 

**Sharing a Wish List:** If you choose to share your WishList, you may provide us with a list of e-mails for family members and friends. You can then send your WishList to anyone on your list. The recipients will not be added to any of our mailings and they will not receive e-mails from All Aboard Toys other than WishList notifications requested directly by the WishList owner. By sharing your WishList, you are authorizing All Aboard Toys to share your e-mail address with your friends and family. 

**Contacting All Aboard Toys Customer Service:** If you contact All Aboard Toys customer service, we will use your name, e-mail address, phone number and order history to answer your question as quickly as possible. On occasion, we may contact you later to verify information or to check on the quality of and experience with your Customer Service contact at All Aboard Toys. 

**Birthday Club Mailings:** If you join our Birthday Club, we collect the e-mail address of a parent, guardian, or family member of a child as well as the child's first name, and the date of birth (not the year, just the day & month). 

**Do you sell or share any of the collected personal information with third parties?**  
We may share customer information with service providers to conduct business on behalf of All Aboard Toys. This includes, but is not limited to, payment authorization and processing companies, customer service providers and shippers. We may disclose aggregate, non-identifiable customer information (such as number of visits or average order amounts) to other third parties. We use a third party system for tracking purposes and information gathered through this system which is not made available to others, only to All Aboard Toys and its agents. 

We may release customer account or other information if we're advised that release is necessary to comply with or as required by law, or to protect the rights, property and safety of All Aboard Toys, our customers or others. This may include the exchange of information with companies and organizations or law enforcement agencies for loss prevention and credit risk reduction. In the event of a bankruptcy, insolvency, merger or acquisition, customer information, including personal information, may be transferred. 

**How do you verify that your web site is secure?**  
We use third party verification tools and outsourced security services to verify that our web site and systems remain safe and well protected. We keep our systems safe by applying security updates as they become available and by constant monitoring of our systems and network. 

**Which technologies do you employ to protect my personal information?**  
At All Aboard Toys, we use the security features of SSL encryption used with a Verisign Secure Server Certificate to protect your personal information while browsing our web site. Sensitive personal information is encrypted using proven, industrial strength strong encryption algorithms. Only the information that is absolutely necessary is kept on file. Information such as credit card numbers are discarded (deleted) when no longer needed for the ordering process. 

You will know you're in the "secure" area of our website when you click on the "Checkout" button. Notice that the "http" portion of the web site address in your browser changes to "https." The "s" stands for "secure." In addition, both Netscape and Internet Explorer use special symbols to indicate that you are in a web site's secure area. Earlier versions of Netscape use a highlighted key. More recent versions of Netscape and all versions of Internet Explorer show a closed, highlighted lock. Some browsers let you know that you are moving in or out of a secure area by notifying you with a special pop-up window that requires you to click "ok" before continuing. 

Protecting your password: We take reasonable precautions to limit unauthorized access to your account. If you forget your password, you can create a new one. However we will provide a password if you request it. You can do your part to protect your personal information by keeping your password a secret and making sure you log off completely if you share a computer. 

**Who has access to my information?**  
There are very few staff members who have access to your personal information. Our back office systems are very secure and access to personal information is only granted to people who handle customer accounts for ordering and returns purposes. 

**What about children's privacy?**  
All Aboard Toys does not knowingly solicit or collect personally identifiable information online from children under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parent consent. Our birthday club only collects a first name and a birth date (without a birth-year) for children. Associated e-mail addresses should be for adults, such as parents, guardians or other family members and not for the child in question. If you feel you have submitted what could be considered personal information for a person less than 13 years of age, please send us an email, and we will take all reasonable measures to delete such information from our databases and to not use such information for any purpose (except where necessary to protect the safety of the child or others as required by law). 

If you child subscribes to one of our e-mail subscriptions such as our Newsletters or Birthday Club services without your knowledge, follow the unsubscribe instructions contained within our e-mails and unsubscribe immediately. If you want more information about children's privacy online, you can consult the AAT Consumer Protection page on the Federal Trade Commission site. 

**Are you using 'Cookies'? What do you use them for?**  
We currently use two kinds of Cookies:  
1) One Cookie generated by All Aboard Toys is to track the state your shopping experience is in and to protect you when using a computer that is shared with more than one person. We do not store any sensitive information inside the Cookie.  
2) Another type of Cookie is used to track your shopping experience and will help us analyze which marketing methods work best. See the next two items for more information. 

**Can I turn the use of 'Cookies' off and still shop on All Aboard Toys?**  
Unfortunately, the answer is 'no'. While you may browse the entire web site without the use of Cookies, currently you must have cookies enabled to order products from All Aboard Toys. 

**Are you tracking my shopping behavior?**  
Our web site and newsletters have so-called Action Tags embedded in them. They allow us to see which methods of marketing work best and allow us to calculate the ROI (Return On Investment) for each method used. We do not engage in unethical marketing methods. In addition, we don't use these Action Tags to track individual shopping behavior and do not associate this information with individuals (customers) but rather use aggregate data to make decisions in terms of which marketing methods to use. 

**Do you send out so called 'spam' or allow anyone else to send me unsolicited e-mail?**  
The answer is simply 'no'. We do not send out unsolicited e-mail, nor do we make your e-mail address or other personal information available to other parties for the purpose of marketing. People that receive our e-mails and newsletters have opted-in through our web site in most cases. If your e-mail address is on our e-mail list and you no longer wish to receive any newsletters from us, just follow the instructions at the bottom of the e-mail to unsubscribe. 

**Who should I contact about questions or concerns regarding my privacy on All Aboard Toys?**  
You may send concerns, feedback or questions regarding your privacy on our website to [ privacy@allaboardtoys.com](mailto:privacy@allaboardtoys.com). We take your privacy and security very serious. We make every effort to review each and every e-mail and to follow-up if appropriate. 

**How can I change my personal information?**  
If you have an account on the All Aboard Toys web site, you may change your personal information at any time by logging in to the account using the 'My Account' link at the top-right of the main page. Should you have misplaced your password needed to log in, please click the appropriate link to retrieve it. 

**Does this privacy policy change? How will I know it has changed?**  
This privacy policy may change at any time, without notice. If we decide to make changes, it is usually to better protect our customer's privacy. The date at the bottom of this document indicates when changes were last made to this policy. 

**Last updated: 5/14/2009**
